Guide to the Roy Edwin Ramseier Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Roy Edwin Ramseier papers
1912-1981
1950-1975
WA MSS S-3242
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
19
(19 boxes) + 247 broadside
The collection consists of reports, project documents, and technical drawings relating to water and sewage projects in California and Nevada, as well as other business and academic records documenting Roy Edwin Ramseier's career as a civil engineer between the 1950s and 1980s. Ramseier's papers document sanitation and water use in California and Nevada, particularly relating to suburbanization and small unincorporated communities. Ramseier also completed projects for private housing developments, government agencies, and businesses. The collection contains particularly thorough documentation of Beatty, Nevada and Valley Springs, California. There are also records relating to Squaw Valley, California, the site of the 1960 winter Olympics, where Ramseier worked on projects before and after the Olympic games.
Ramseier, Roy Edwin
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Marc Selvaggio, Bookseller on the Frederick W. and Carrie S. Beinecke Fund for Western Americana, 2016.
Arrangement
Organized into four series: I. California Projects, 1926-1980. II. Nevada Projects, 1958-1978. III. Business Records and Academic Writings, 1912-1981. IV. Technical Drawings, 1935-1980.
Roy Edwin Ramseier (1912-2010)
Roy Edwin Ramseier (1912-2010) was a civil engineer who worked primarily on water and sewage projects in California and Nevada from the 1950s to 1980s. The son of a civil engineer, Ramseier studied engineering at the University of California, Berkeley. He established his business, Roy Edwin Ramseier and Associates, in Berkeley and remained in California for the entirety of his career. Ramseier also wrote several articles on air testing for sewers.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of reports, project documents, and blueprints relating to water and sewage projects in California and Nevada, as well as other business and academic records documenting Roy Edwin Ramseier's career as a civil engineer between the 1950s and 1980s. Ramseier's papers document sanitation and water use in California and Nevada, particularly relating to suburbanization and small unincorporated communities. Ramseier also completed projects for private housing developments, government agencies, and businesses. The collection contains particularly thorough documentation of Beatty, Nevada and Valley Springs, California. There are also records relating to Squaw Valley, California, the site of the 1960 winter Olympics, where Ramseier worked on projects before and after the Olympic games.
Civil engineering -- Nevada; Planned communities -- California; Planned communities -- Nevada; Engineering drawings; Civil engineering -- California; Engineers -- California; Sewerage -- California; Sewerage -- Nevada; Sewer districts -- California; Sewer districts -- Nevada; Water use -- California; Water use -- Nevada; Valley Springs (Calif.); Beatty (Nev.); Squaw Valley (Calif.); Technical drawings; Ramseier, Roy Edwin
- California Projects, 1926-1980; Series I; 11; 11 boxes
  Arrangement
  Arranged by project. Within each project, original order has been maintained.
  Scope and Contents
  The series comprises project documents, correspondence, and reports concerning Roy Edwin Ramseier's sewage and water projects in California. Ramseier's California clients included cities, planned communities, businesses, hospitals, and private residences. There is significant documentation of projects in Valley Springs, California. Other projects include Squaw Valley, California, the site of the 1960 winter Olympics.
  - East Bay Regional Park District, 1965-1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - East Bay Regional Park District Don Castro Recreation Area, 1971-1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - East Bay Regional Park, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - East Bay Regional Parks District Tilden Park Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - East Bay Regional Parks District Tilden Park Correspondence, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - East Bay Regional Park District Alameda Memorial State Beach and Contra Loma Regional Park, 1968-1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - [East Bay Regional Park District Sewage Companies and Equipment], 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - East Bay Regional Park District, 1965-1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Castlewood Country Club, 1953-1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - [San Andreas Sanitary District Sewage Projects], 1947-1958 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Pollution Survey of Lake Merritt, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - [City of Dunsmuir], 1926-1955 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Dunsmuir, 1940-1951 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - [Squaw Valley Mutual Water Company Invoices], 1957-1963 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - [Squaw Valley Mutual Water Company Invoices and Improvement Plan], 1957-1973 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Squaw Valley Mutual Water Company, Greenwood, 1964-1974 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Squaw Valley George's Report, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Squaw Valley Water and Sewage, 1956-1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Squaw Valley Greenwood, 1974-1978 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Squaw Valley Design Notes, 1963-1972 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Diablo Valley College Brochure, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Diablo Valley College, 1951-1972 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Diablo Valley College Design Notes, 1959-1963 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Preliminary Report on Irrigation System for Gregory Gardens County Water District, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Specifications for Gregory Gardens County Water District Water Distribution System, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Gregory Gardens, 1951-1953 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - [Central Contra Costa Sanitary District Correspondence, Plans, and Clippings], 1953-1956 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - [Contra Costa County, Oakley Sanitary District Reports], 1952-1956 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Cameo Acres, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - [Eden Township Drain Ditches, Culverts, and Dyke], 1931 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Glass Mountain Ranch Swimming Pool, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Alpine Springs, 1961-1969 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - [Ostwald Residence, Los Gatos], 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Twain Harte Motels, Inc., 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Dow Chemical, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - City of Martinez, 1966-1971 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Pleasanton, 1946-1957 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Pleasanton Sewage, 1947-1957 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Freestone Water System, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - [City of Albany Storm Drains], 1960 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Weldwood, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Fruitvale Canning Co., 1952 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Mark Twain Hospital, 1950-1954 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Simplex Manufacturing Co., 1960 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Winding Creek Mutual Water Co., 1963-1966 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - White Sulfur Springs, 1967-1971 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - [Decoto Sewage System], 1936-1939 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Spruce Point, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Imperial Valley Farms, 1936-1937 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Water Service for Castle Rock County Water District, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Hoehner Packing Co., 1955 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Ward Well Water Co., 1958-1960 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - City of Berkeley, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Survey of Wastes Disposal at H. J. Heinz Company Berkeley, California, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Investigation of the Lake Chabot Water Supply of Vallejo Water Co., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Imperial County Health Department, 1936-1956 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Manteca Canning Co., 1947-1950 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Pla-Vada, 1955-1974 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Independent Farm and Businessmen's Club, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - International Paper Co., 1958 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - North Tahoe Public Utility District, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Hagginwood Sanitary District, 1951-1953 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - [Winston Manor], 1955-1957 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - [Contra Loma Swimming Complex], 1976-1980 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - [Djerassi Residence], 1970 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Horseshoe Hill, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Chauvet Water Works, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Occidental Community Services District, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Tahoe Southside Water Utility, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Tahoe Southside Design Notes, 1969-1974 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Tahoe Southside, 1958-1975 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Manure Clarification Device at the Dairy Barn of Fairmont Hospital in Alameda County, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - [Berryessa Water Company], 1958-1964 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Ground Cow Restaurant, 1962-1968 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - [Contra Costa Junior College District, Diablo Valley College], 1959-1967 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Contra Costa College, 1965-1972 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - [Valley Springs Sanitary District], 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Valley Springs, 1969-1973 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - [Valley Springs Sanitary District], 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 79-80)
  - Valley Springs, 1972-1977 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Valley Springs Sanitary District Audit Reports and Financial Statements, 1969-1974 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Valley Springs, 1949-1975 (Box 8, Folder 83-89)
  - Nicasio, 1972-1975 (Box 9, Folder 90-91)
  - [Nicasio Notes and Drawings], circa 1972-1975 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Tamarack Mutual Water Company, 1969-1972 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - [City of Paso Robles], 1947-1960 (Box 9, Folder 94-95)
  - Paso Robles Design Notes, 1947-1960 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - [Paso Robles Correspondence], 1954-1966 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Paso Robles, 1941-1960 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - [Niles Sanitary District], 1939-1949 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - [Niles Sanitary District Photographs], circa 1939-1949 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Meadowood, 1962-1969 (Box 10, Folder 101-103)
  - Meadowood Design, 1961-1963 (Box 11, Folder 104)
  - Meadowood, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 105)
  - Mokelumne Hill, 1946-1949 (Box 11, Folder 106)
  - [Mokelumne Hill Correspondence], 1954-1959 (Box 11, Folder 107)
  - Yreka, 1949-1953 (Box 11, Folder 108)
  - Yreka, 1953-1956 (Box 11, Folder 109)
  - Tahoe Pines, 1949-1964 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - [Irvington Sanitary District], 1946-1950 (Box 11, Folder 111)
  - Inverness Water Works, 1948-1973 (Box 11, Folder 112)
  - [California Lab Reports], 1959-1972 (Box 12, Folder 113-114)
- Nevada Projects, 1958-1978; Series II; 5; (5 boxes)
  The series comprises project documents, correspondence, and reports concerning Roy Edwin Ramseier's sewage and water projects in Nevada. Ramseier's Nevada clients were mostly cities and small towns, notably Beatty and Minden-Gardnerville. Other projects involved mines and ranches.
  - [Beatty Water and Sanitation District], 1971-1974 (Box 12, Folder 115)
  - Beatty Survey Notes, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 116)
  - [Beatty Notes and Plans], 1968-1975 (Box 12, Folder 117)
  - Operation and Maintenance Manual for Beatty Water and Sanitation District, 1974-1976 (Box 12, Folder 118)
  - Preliminary Report on Waste Water Collection, Treatment, and Disposal for Beatty Water and Sanitation District, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 119)
  - [Beatty Water and Sanitation District], 1974-1978 (Box 12, Folder 120)
  - Beatty, 1963-1973 (Box 12, Folder 121-122)
  - Beatty Water, 1964-1967 (Box 13, Folder 123)
  - [Beatty Water and Sanitation District], 1963-1975 (Box 13, Folder 124)
  - [Beatty Notes and Plans], 1975 (Box 13, Folder 125)
  - [Beatty Water and Sanitation District], 1960-1974 (Box 13, Folder 126)
  - Operation and Maintenance Manual for Beatty Water and Sanitation District, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 127)
  - Beatty, 1962-1969 (Box 13, Folder 128)
  - Beatty Sewer, 1967-1974 (Box 14, Folder 129)
  - [Beatty Water and Sanitation District], 1967 (Box 14, Folder 130)
  - Beatty Record of Pre-Construction Conference, undated (Box 14, Folder 131)
  - [Beatty Bid], 1975 (Box 14, Folder 132)
  - [Beatty Water and Sanitation District], 1975-1978 (Box 14, Folder 133)
  - Environmental Assessment of Waste Water Treatment Plant proposed for Beatty Water and Sanitation District, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 134)
  - Beatty Water, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 135)
  - [Beatty Water and Sanitation District], 1970-1974 (Box 14, Folder 136)
  - [Beatty Manholes and Drains], 1975 (Box 15, Folder 137)
  - [Fernley Sanitation District], 1964-1968 (Box 15, Folder 138)
  - Fernley, 1964-1974 (Box 15, Folder 139)
  - Fernley Design Notes, 1964-1969 (Box 15, Folder 140)
  - B-Neva, 1961-1964 (Box 16, Folder 141)
  - [Minden-Gardnerville Sanitation District], 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 142-143)
  - Minden-Gardnerville Design Notes, 1964-1965 (Box 16, Folder 144)
  - Minden-Gardnerville Brochure, 1964-1965 (Box 16, Folder 145)
  - [Minden-Gardnerville Sanitation District], 1963-1965 (Box 16, Folder 146)
  - Minden-Gardnerville, 1958-1969 (Box 17, Folder 147)
  - Clark County Fluoridation Study, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 148)
  - Crystal Shore, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 149)
  - Lovelock Design Notes, 1960-1965 (Box 17, Folder 150)
  - [Lovelock], 1960-1967 (Box 17, Folder 151)
  - Lovelock Brochure, 1960-1965 (Box 17, Folder 152)
  - Lovelock, 1962-1968 (Box 18, Folder 153)
  - Lincoln Valley Ranch Proposed Waste Water Reclamation, 1960-1967 (Box 18, Folder 154)
  - Cordero Mine, 1966-1968 (Box 18, Folder 155)
- Business Records and Academic Writings, 1912-1981; Series III; 2; (2 boxes)
  Original order has been maintained.
  The series comprises the business records of Roy Edwin Ramseier and Associates and the academic records and writings of Roy Edwin Ramseier. Business records include invoices, tax records, and expense accounts. Academic records include Ramseier's academic writings about air testing for sewers and articles he collected about civil engineering, sewers, and water testing. Also included is a folder of the professional and personal records of Irvin B. Ramseier, Roy Edwin Ramseier's father, who was also a civil engineer.
  - Langelier Index, undated (Box 18, Folder 156)
  - [Cole Pitometer System Articles], 1940-1945 (Box 18, Folder 157)
  - Invoices, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 158)
  - Invoices, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 159)
  - Expense Accounts, 1949-1952 (Box 18, Folder 160)
  - Office Building Taxes, 1957-1970 (Box 18, Folder 161)
  - Greenwood Invoices, 1964-1967 (Box 18, Folder 162)
  - Practical Automation, Inc., undated (Box 18, Folder 163)
  - [Financial Records], 1954-1963 (Box 18, Folder 164)
  - Old Bills, 1961-1964 (Box 18, Folder 165)
  - Paid Bills, 1969-1970 (Box 18, Folder 166)
  - Office Bills and Plans, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 167)
  - [Central Engineering Associated Business Correspondence], 1981 (Box 19, Folder 168)
  - [Tariffs and Rates], 1943-1977 (Box 19, Folder 169)
  - Uni-Bell Plastic Pipe Association, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 170)
  - [Operation and Service Manuals], 1966-1975 (Box 19, Folder 171)
  - The Evaluation of Industrial Wastes in the East Bay, 1942 (Box 19, Folder 172)
  - [Bio-Infiltration Paper], undated (Box 19, Folder 173)
  - Experience in Using the Low Pressure Air Test for Sanitary Sewers, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 174)
  - Air Test, 1961-1971 (Box 19, Folder 175)
  - [Nevada Ground Water Report], 1962 (Box 19, Folder 176)
  - [California Mosquito Reports], 1932-1937 (Box 19, Folder 177)
  - Alta Vista Sanitary Survey, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 178)
  - Report to General Electric Co. on the Vallecitos Atomic Laboratory Waste Discharge Treatment Facility, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 179)
  - Hardy Cross, 1936-1943 (Box 19, Folder 180)
  - Infiltration/Inflow Study Mare Island Naval Shipyard Vallejo, California, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 181)
  - Soil Investigation West Shore Export Facility Lake Tahoe, California, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 182)
  - Measuring Water in Irrigation Channels U.S. Departmen of Agriculture Farmers' Bulletin No. 1683, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 183)
  - Federal Communications Commission Rules and Regulations, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 184)
  - [Irvin B. Ramseier], 1912-1950 (Box 19, Folder 185)
- Technical Drawings, 1935-1980; Series IV
  Arranged by project.
  General
  Several technical drawings were removed from binders labeled with the project name.
  Circa 1,200 technical drawings documenting Ramseier's career and engineering projects in California and Nevada, 1935-1980.
  - Alpine Meadows Ski Area, 1961-1962 (Box 20 (Broadside))
  - Alpine Meadows Ski Area, 1961-1962 (Box 21 (Broadside))
  - Alpine Meadows Ski Area, 1961-1962 (Box 22 (Broadside))
  - Alpine Meadows Ski Area, 1961-1962 (Box 23 (Broadside))
  - Placer County, California, 1961-1967 (Box 24 (Broadside))
  - Placer County, California, 1961-1967 (Box 25 (Broadside))
  - Placer County, California, 1961-1967 (Box 26 (Broadside))
  - Placer County, California, 1961-1967 (Box 27 (Broadside))
  - Placer County, California, 1961-1967 (Box 28 (Broadside))
  - Placer County, California, 1961-1967 (Box 29 (Broadside))
  - Placer County, California, 1961-1967 (Box 30 (Broadside))
  - Placer County, California, 1961-1967 (Box 31 (Broadside))
  - Placer County, California, 1961-1967 (Box 32 (Broadside))
  - Placer County, California, 1961-1967 (Box 33 (Broadside))
  - Placer County, California, 1961-1967 (Box 34 (Broadside))
  - Placer County, California, 1961-1967 (Box 35 (Broadside))
  - Placer County, California, 1961-1967 (Box 36 (Broadside))
  - Placer County, California, 1961-1967 (Box 37 (Broadside))
  - East Bay Regional Park District, 1976 (Box 38 (Broadside))
  - Unidentified projects, undated (Box 39 (Broadside))
  - Unidentified projects, undated (Box 40 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 41 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 42 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 43 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 44 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 45 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 46 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 47 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 48 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 49 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 50 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 51 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 52 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 53 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 54 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 55 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 56 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 57 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 58 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 59 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 60 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 61 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 62 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 63 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 64 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 65 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 66 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 67 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 68 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 69 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 70 (Broadside))
  - Beatty, Nevada, 1959-1977 (Box 71 (Broadside))
  - Oakley County, California Water District, 1955-1977 (Box 72 (Broadside))
  - Oakley County, California Water District, 1955-1977 (Box 73 (Broadside))
  - Oakley County, California Water District, 1955-1977 (Box 74 (Broadside))
  - Oakley County, California Water District, 1955-1977 (Box 75 (Broadside))
  - Oakley County, California Water District, 1955-1977 (Box 76 (Broadside))
  - Oakley County, California Water District, 1955-1977 (Box 77 (Broadside))
  - Oakley County, California Water District, 1955-1977 (Box 78 (Broadside))
  - Oakley County, California Water District, 1955-1977 (Box 79 (Broadside))
  - Oakley County, California Water District, 1955-1977 (Box 80 (Broadside))
  - Oakley County, California Water District, 1955-1977 (Box 81 (Broadside))
  - Oakley County, California Water District, 1955-1977 (Box 82 (Broadside))
  - Oakley County, California Water District, 1955-1977 (Box 83 (Broadside))
  - Oakley County, California Water District, 1955-1977 (Box 84 (Broadside))
  - Oakley County, California Water District, 1955-1977 (Box 85 (Broadside))
  - Oakley County, California Water District, 1955-1977 (Box 86 (Broadside))
  - Oakley County, California Water District, 1955-1977 (Box 87 (Broadside))
  - Oakley County, California Water District, 1955-1977 (Box 88 (Broadside))
  - Oakley County, California Water District, 1955-1977 (Box 89 (Broadside))
  - Oakley County, California Water District, 1955-1977 (Box 90 (Broadside))
  - Oakley County, California Water District, 1955-1977 (Box 91 (Broadside))
  - Oakley County, California Water District, 1955-1977 (Box 92 (Broadside))
  - Oakley County, California Water District, 1955-1977 (Box 93 (Broadside))
  - Oakley County, California Water District, 1955-1977 (Box 94 (Broadside))
  - Oakley County, California Water District, 1955-1977 (Box 95 (Broadside))
  - B-Neva, Inc., 1960-1964 (Box 96 (Broadside))
  - B-Neva, Inc., 1960-1964 (Box 97 (Broadside))
  - B-Neva, Inc., 1960-1964 (Box 98 (Broadside))
  - B-Neva, Inc., 1960-1964 (Box 99 (Broadside))
  - B-Neva, Inc., 1960-1964 (Box 100 (Broadside))
  - B-Neva, Inc., 1960-1964 (Box 101 (Broadside))
  - Minden-Gardnerville Sanitation District, Nevada, 1965 (Box 102 (Broadside))
  - San Andreas, California Sanitary Department, 1954-1955 (Box 103 (Broadside))
  - Crystal Shore, Lake Tahoe, 1972-1975 (Box 104 (Broadside))
  - Crystal Shore, Lake Tahoe, 1972-1975 (Box 105 (Broadside))
  - Crystal Shore, Lake Tahoe, 1972-1975 (Box 106 (Broadside))
  - Crystal Shore, Lake Tahoe, 1972-1975 (Box 107 (Broadside))
  - Crystal Shore, Lake Tahoe, 1972-1975 (Box 108 (Broadside))
  - Crystal Shore, Lake Tahoe, 1972-1975 (Box 109 (Broadside))
  - Crystal Shore, Lake Tahoe, 1972-1975 (Box 110 (Broadside))
  - Retaining Wall Designs, 1935 (Box 111 (Broadside))
  - Los Angeles County Sanitation Districts, 1947 (Box 112 (Broadside))
  - Nicasio Ridge, 1973 (Box 113 (Broadside))
  - Valley Springs, California, 1969-1977 (Box 114 (Broadside))
  - Valley Springs, California, 1969-1977 (Box 115 (Broadside))
  - Valley Springs, California, 1969-1977 (Box 116 (Broadside))
  - Valley Springs, California, 1969-1977 (Box 117 (Broadside))
  - Valley Springs, California, 1969-1977 (Box 118 (Broadside))
  - Valley Springs, California, 1969-1977 (Box 119 (Broadside))
  - Valley Springs, California, 1969-1977 (Box 120 (Broadside))
  - Valley Springs, California, 1969-1977 (Box 121 (Broadside))
  - Valley Springs, California, 1969-1977 (Box 122 (Broadside))
  - Valley Springs, California, 1969-1977 (Box 123 (Broadside))
  - Valley Springs, California, 1969-1977 (Box 124 (Broadside))
  - Valley Springs, California, 1969-1977 (Box 125 (Broadside))
  - Valley Springs, California, 1969-1977 (Box 126 (Broadside))
  - Valley Springs, California, 1969-1977 (Box 127 (Broadside))
  - Valley Springs, California, 1969-1977 (Box 128 (Broadside))
  - Valley Springs, California, 1969-1977 (Box 129 (Broadside))
  - Valley Springs, California, 1969-1977 (Box 130 (Broadside))
  - Ground Cow, Inc., 1962 (Box 131 (Broadside))
  - Ground Cow, Inc., 1962 (Box 132 (Broadside))
  - Ground Cow, Inc., 1962 (Box 133 (Broadside))
  - Ground Cow, Inc., 1962 (Box 134 (Broadside))
  - Ground Cow, Inc., 1962 (Box 135 (Broadside))
  - Ground Cow, Inc., 1962 (Box 136 (Broadside))
  - Ground Cow, Inc., 1962 (Box 137 (Broadside))
  - Ground Cow, Inc., 1962 (Box 138 (Broadside))
  - Fernley, Nevada, 1964-1969 (Box 139 (Broadside))
  - Fernley, Nevada, 1964-1969 (Box 140 (Broadside))
  - Fernley, Nevada, 1964-1969 (Box 141 (Broadside))
  - Fernley, Nevada, 1964-1969 (Box 142 (Broadside))
  - Fernley, Nevada, 1964-1969 (Box 143 (Broadside))
  - Fernley, Nevada, 1964-1969 (Box 144 (Broadside))
  - Fernley, Nevada, 1964-1969 (Box 145 (Broadside))
  - Fernley, Nevada, 1964-1969 (Box 146 (Broadside))